I have had a long life.
Because I've lived so long, I've learned
that the world is beyond my control.
So I fought.
As ruler, as protector, as heir...
I fought, and fought, and kept fighting...
Let's stop this stupid war.
I'd rather sit down and have a talk with you.
Setsu...
Here.
What is this?
A token of reconciliation.
I think black would look great on you, Dezas.
Setsu...
I thought what I needed
to do to live my life
was give up what makes me me.
Evilbarrow, Castelul Lordului Întunericului
Missing?
Yes.
We did all we could, but couldn't find him.
It seems like Distinia has
no idea where he is, either.
Enough.
Even if we never meet again, I will keep
the promise of peace I made to you...
Setsu.
We did strike a peace deal,
but there's still much to do before
we achieve true, lasting peace.
We must redouble our efforts, Vlad.
Yes! I, Vlad, will lay down my life for this!
Lord Dezastol!
We have fresh fruit from Distinia today!
My lord! The meat from my homeland
is fresh and tasty, too!
It has been five years
since the end of the war.
It's great to see our
nation prosper like this.
Yes. Everyone worked so hard. War is—
My lord?
Perhaps I've spent too much time wearing it.
I heard there is a skilled
jeweler in Distinia.
I'll send it out for repairs.
Thank you. Sorry to send
you on a personal errand.
Episodul 4
Primind pentru a doua oară un cadou
Reporting! A Distinian army has
appeared and invaded us!
Battle rages as we speak,
just outside of Evilbarrow!
Only five years after the peace charter?
How frail this peace was.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
Gather all the top officers immediately!
We will prepare our army!
Yes, my lord!
Zeon and Lamina,
head to Distinia immediately.
Something is suspicious.
We must first find out what's going on.
Yes, my lord!
Setsu, I will keep our promise.
No matter what.
Weapons go in the first warehouse, food and
medicine to the second warehouse! Hurry!
We have to return to the
front lines right away.
Who knows if we'll come
back alive this time...
So there are huge, armored enemies
that weren't there five years ago?
What did we sign that peace charter for?
We should never have trusted the humans.
If a full-on war breaks out and
destroys our supply chain, we'll...
It's fine! As long as we buy her some time,
the Demon Lord will take care of this.
Even after a month,
there's been no contact from Distinia...
We're holding the line for now,
but our nation won't last long at this rate.
Am I incapable of keeping
my promise to Setsu?
Excuse me.
Vlad. What is it?
Terran Sneeter from the Terran Trading
Company requests an audience with you.
Terran himself?
Well, I can't turn him away.
Let him in.
Yes, my lord.
Are you crazy?!
Watch what you say, lowly human!
Oh, no. I am completely serious.
This is a sincere offer.
I would like to use the power of Terran
Trading to help end the war with Distinia.
What more could a ruler ask for?
Using your wealth, purported
to be the greatest in the world?
Yes. To be honest, I feel we can end
the war outright, not just offer help.
That's how powerful the
Terran Trading Company is.
And in return, you would ask...
To have you become my wife,
Dezastol Serreno. Precisely.
You must mean your slave.
If it means having your beauty in my grasp,
then you may call it whatever you wish.
Here is the necklace on which
we will swear our vows.
A curse of servitude?! And so powerful...
It seems you came well prepared.
Where did you get such a thing?
It did require some effort on my part,
but it was all in the name of my love for you.
My lord, do not even entertain such nonsense!
We must immediately take this fool and—
Give me some time to think.
My lord!
I have all the time in the world.
But I wonder...
Do you have that kind of time?
Is this the only way I can
keep my promise to you?
My lord...
I thought I asked everyone to leave.
There's no need for you to
accept that ridiculous offer.
Your army is ready to fight to the
last man for you, myself included.
I know. That's why I can't refuse.
Do you think me a foolish woman,
unworthy of being the Demon Lord?
I won't give up. Please excuse me.
You told me black would look good on me.
Will you laugh when you see me wear
white against my wishes, Setsu?
Dezastol was easier to
convince than I expected.
It seems lending aid to your schemes through
the Terran Trading Company will pay off.
Now the demonic kingdom is ours.
If we push any further,
we might start a tiresome war.
Should we pull back those
expensive magic soldiers?
No need.
Why not? You want the demonic kingdom,
I want the beautiful Demon Lord.
This deal is settled, is it not?
Because it is the will of my master.
Ziua nunții
So beautiful!
Groom, Terran Sneeter, and bride,
Dezastol Serreno.
You may now exchange your vows of love.
I, Terran Sneeter, and
Demon Lord Dezastol Serreno,
swear today to enter into a
vow of master and servant!
And the Terran Trading Company,
through the annexation
of the power of the demonic
kingdom of Eviltheon,
vows to bring eternal prosperity
and everlasting peace to the world!
Now, my compatriots!
Pledge your allegiance to me,
your new Demon Lord,
and together we will protect the world
and leave our names in the history books!
Now, enough theatrics.
Dezastol Serreno, you will vow
eternal love to me, Terran.
If only I could see you
one last time... Setsu...
C-Ce?!
O explozie?! Suntem atacați?!
Sunt aici ca să te salvez, prințesă.
Setsu!
Vlad, privește!
Acela e Setsu, nu-i așa?
He's as over-the-top as ever.
Să ne grăbim.
C-Ce naiba ești?!
What are you?!
Fools! Do your job! Protect me!
Levia!
Dezas, chiar nu-ți
stă deloc bine în alb.
You should give up on
wearing a wedding dress.
Shadow Magic: Shadow Stab.
Nu mă pot mișca?!
The god of the seas isn't
too impressive on land, I see.
Oprește-te!
So, ready to pay for making Dezas cry?
I wasn't expecting Setsu the Hero to show up.
I'll have quite the report to give my master!
Your master?
What?!
Is that it? You're not even trying.
You are indeed strong,
but today I must prioritize
notifying my master.
We'll settle this later, Setsu the Hero.
Damn it, he got away.
Setsu!
I missed you! I missed you, Setsu!
Where did you go without me?!
Y-Yeah, that's a long story...
Anyway, I'm glad you're safe, Dezas.
Yes!
Uh, sorry to interrupt this
touching reunion, but...
Magic soldiers made from curses...
These curses... I guess it really
must be Toma behind the scenes.
I suspected it might be possible.
So it really is Toma, then.
Then, as Demon Lord,
I must lend you aid, Setsu!
He needs to pay for making me wear this.
I'll let you handle things here, then.
I'll go visit Regulus.
There's no telling what Toma might try.
The Beastmen...
Yes, securing the aid of Regulus, King of
the Beastmen, would be most reassuring.
But this all seems very rushed.
We do have a promise of peace to keep.
Yes.
We must do this, for our promise.
Wait, are we leaving right away?
Am I on ferry duty again?
I've been running around fighting all night!
Setsu-san!
Oh, no! The castle is a mess!
Did everything work out?
Yeah. It was pretty close, though.
You should be the one to give this to her.
It's important, right?
Yeah, thanks.
Setsu?
This makes another second time.
Yes, the second time.
That's right.
Once again, you've taught me
what it means to live.
I would have loved to accompany you,
but this is no time for the
ruler to leave her throne.
Yeah. Once we get back to peace,
I'll take you wherever you want.
Yes. That's a promise.
Well, um... Just because it's peacetime
doesn't mean the ruler can leave the country...
That's where you come in.
Don't make Dezas do all the work.
Yes.
The Demon Lord kindly allowed
me to open a shop here!
My very own shop! It's my dream come true!
Are you sure?
She delivered my precious brooch.
It's the least I could do.
Thanks for the help, Setsu.
If you need anything,
we will race to your side.
Yeah. I'll be counting on you.
All right, ready to go?
Oh, very well.
I'll tag along with you, no matter how far!
Yeah!
Be sure to come straight
back to me once it's all over!
Yeah, see you soon!
Data viitoare
Călcându-i pentru a doua oară pe urme
Data viitoare: Călcându-i
pentru a doua oară pe urme.